JOSEPH NARTEY

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Phone: 0540539205

Email: joenart2@gmail.com

I'm a knowledgeable fullstack developer who loves creating successful websites that meets customer needs. Specializing in collaborating with customers to gather requirements, produce plans, improve design for usability and functionality. Fully proficient in React JS, Javascript, HTML and CSS, Node JS, Laravel and MongoDB. Visit my website at devjoemedia.com to see what I can do.

Skills

HTML and CSS

Javascript

Reactjs

Node JS

MongoDB

Laravel

Work History

2017-2018 Minsherick Acadamy

Role: Teacher

2018-2021 Tedusa ventures

Role: Manager

Education | Certificates

2014-2017 WEST AFRICA SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE EXAMS (WASSCE)

Institution: Ningo Senior secondary school – old Ningo

2019-08 NODEJS CERTIFICATION

Institution: Udemy – US by Jonas schmmendmant